Ibnul Ashir

Web Developer



6/1, North Adabor, Shymoli, Dhaka-1205



+8801765427688



ibnulashir42@gmail.com



ibnul-ashir/



A highly motivated programmer, innovative thinker with strong logical, analytical and leading skills, with the ability to work as a team. An expert in with strong familiarity in software engineering concepts, my strength in these areas will be very helpful in developing software applications for relative works.



Skills



Technical Skills

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- React JS, Next JS
- Bootstrap, Material UI
- Tailwind CSS, SCSS

Programming Skills

200 + accepted solutions at Online Judge

- <u>Uri-online-judge/</u>
- Leet-code/

- Node JS, Express JS
- SQL Server, Mongo DB



Work Experiences



February, 2022 - Present

Frontend Developer

- Frontend development according to the requirements.
- Fixing Cascading style sheets.
- Design and developed dashboard as well as client side section.
- Dynamic UI and development according to the requirement's.
- Technology stake React JS, RESTful API, Node JS, Mongo DB, React Router DOM.



Work Experiences

iSharify LTD.

December, 2019 - March, 2020

Project Manager

- R&D on reporting tool.
- Product development according to the requirements.
- In house production solution.

Raspberry ERP

June, 2020- February, 2021

Frontend Developer

- R&D on different modules of ERP platform.
- Requirement analysis of very configurable ERP solution.
- The main responsibility was the configure user interface with AngularJS and bootstrap, write store procedure in SQL Server.



Education

B.Sc. in Software Engineering

2019

Daffodil International University

Dhaka, Bangladesh.

Higher Secondary Certificate

2014

Aminur Rahman College

Mohammadpur, Magura, Bangladesh.

Secondary School Certificate R.S.K.H Institution

2012

Mohammadpur, Magura, Bangladesh.



Certification and Training

Software Developer Certificate (SDC)

2019

Kovair Software, Inc.

San Ramon, CA 94583, USA

Projects

Aristo Market

Online eCommerce solution React JS, Node JS, Mongo DB Link: github.com/ibnul42/aristo-market-ecommercewebsite

Github Finder

React JS, Express JS, Tailwind CSS, Daisy UI Link: github.com/ibnul42/github-finder

Developer Job Search

React JS, Bootstrap

Link: github.com/ibnu42/developer-job-search

Personal Info

- Nationality: BangladeshiMarital Status: Unmarried
- Language
 - o English Working Proficient
 - o Bangla Native Language

Links

github.com/ibnul42

in linkedin.com/in/Ibnul-ashir

References

Mr. Md. Khaled Sohel

Assistant Professor Mobile: +88 01713493251

Dhaka, Bangladesh.

Ms. Farzana Sadia

Senior Lecturer

Mobile: +88 01973726762 Email: sadia.swe@diu.edu.bd

Dhaka, Bangladesh.